Guide to the Stewart Brand Papers M1237
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series V: Miscellaneous
  - Oversize: articles/photographs re. Counter Culture, ca. 1967 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Oversize: articles/ROTC commission (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Oversize: SOLUX blueprints (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Oversize: "Orchestration for Sensorium Five: America Needs Indians," by Stewart Brand, University of California, Berkeley, May 18, 1965 (Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous publications, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous newsclippings/articles, various dates (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous research publications, various dates (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Series VI: Media
  - Seventeen (17) 7" reel-to-reel tapes, ca. 1964-1969 (Box 117)
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Audio reels have been transferred and are available digitally.
  - Media Lab media: Four (4) audiocassettes; Seventy (70) micro-cassettes (Box 118)
  - How Buildings Learn and Media Lab media: eleven (11) audiocassettes; seventy (70) micro-cassettes; three (3) removable hard disk cartridges (Box 119)
- Series VII: Business records (CLOSED)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Steward Brand's business records are closed until Brand's death.
  - Stock Information, ca. 1962-1968 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    General
    Business Records of Stewart Brand closed
  - Tax and stock documents, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Tax and stock documents, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Tax and stock documents, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Tax and stock documents, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Tax and stock documents, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Tax and stock documents, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Tax and stock documents, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Tax and stock documents, 1970-1971 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Tax documents, 1971 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Tax documents, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Tax documents, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Tax and stock documents, 1980-1981 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Tax and stock documents, 1980-1981 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Financial records, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Financial records, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Business tax documents (Phelan), 1983-1986 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - CMA [Cash Management Account], 1986 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - CMA [Cash Management Account], 1986 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Family tax documents, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Business tax documents, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Financial records, 1986-1987 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Business tax documents, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Family tax documents, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Business tax documents, 1988 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - CMA [Cash Management Account], 1990 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - CMA [Cash Management Account], 1991 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - CMA [Cash Management Account], 1992 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - CMA [Cash Management Account], 1993 (Box 124, Folder 5)